cakes
voodoo
pro BOA
How are you doing, pitcher?
I was a little nervous.
But I think it's best to do it as usual.
Yes, sir.
OH!
I've memorized it, so I'm sure it won't be a problem if I can keep up the form I'm in now on the day.
I understand.
I'm wondering if you can remember that body like a boy.
You're moving like an experienced dancer.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, not at all.
Are you sure?
I'm fine.
I'm glad.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, my God! Yeah!
I'm so happy to get one shot!
I'm super happy!
I thought it would be cool if I was the first one to do it today.
I'm so happy!
It's not often that I can do it so consistently after only one practice last time.
If I run too fast, I accelerate too much.
So I just hold it like I'm going down, and it just goes!
If I hold it all the time, I can't take off anymore.
If I hold it all the time, I lose the timing to release it and it goes all the way.
So when I see the front of this thing, when I think I can reach it, I fly toward it.
I'm going to fly to it.
Wow!
I can't do it!
Why is that?
I'm on the trampoline, but I'm jumping backwards.
I was so focused on the bar.
I lost my balance.
But maybe after I told you that.
My center of gravity.
You look worried.
If Silk Slider says so, it's just a rehearsal.
I don't know how it's going to turn out.
This... this... this...
Please, please, grab me!
I'm begging you, please grab me.
This is my first time doing Sasuke.
I think it's a rare opportunity to practice something that's so close to the real thing.
I think it's a rare opportunity to practice something so close to the real thing in advance.
I'll do my best to complete what I've practiced in this way on the day of the performance.
Thank you, Mr. Matsuda.
This way?
No, no, no, no, thank you.
No, really, it was only twice.
But once I teach him the tricks, he's able to correct them immediately.
He has such potential that I think he's an athlete.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm really looking forward to the show.
Yes, I'm sure you'll tell me.
I will definitely live up to your expectations.
Yes, I'll do my best.
Girls Girls number 20, Yoko Ogawa.
Congratulations.
What's up?
Would you like to be right behind me?
Thank you very much.
Right this way, sir.
Yes, sir.
Yes, please.
I'll make sure it's clear.
Yes, you will.
Isn't the new area scary?
What do you mean?
Did you hear?
What?
Everyone's freaking out.
No, no, no, no, no.
We have to do it, so, you know...
Let's go.
I just watched a little video explaining the rules.
First of all, we're going to go to the Thin Area.
I didn't think they would introduce a thin area here.
I really don't know what's going to happen on the day of the tournament, so I really don't know what to do.
I don't have any countermeasures, so I'm just going to do it on the spot today.
I just have to go with my own feeling.
Other than that, I hope I can do as well as I practiced.
I'm sure I'll be able to make it to the thin area.
Do you think that's an absolute promise?
Yes, that's a promise.
I have the best athletic ability and mental strength in the world.
Mr. Matsuda told me that 90% of Sasaki is mental.
It's difficult in every area.
I hope I can do my best to keep my mentality strong.
I have a strong mental attitude, so I'm not the most nervous I've ever been.
Surprisingly, I think I'll be fine after the first jump.
I'm the type of person who can relax after the first jump.
I think I can take it from there.
That's what I have practiced at Matsuda Park.
It's important to make the best of it.
I'm sure I'll do well if I just give it all I've got.
I'll put the new area aside for now.
But since Mr. Yamamoto just told me about the new area, I think I'll try to follow his advice.
I'm going to try to follow that for now.
But I don't feel nervous at all.
Four crowns as usual.
There's a division of roles.
Give me Matsuya!
What is a toe?
Reach out your hand, Momoka
Yuzu Minami on the side
Look down and you'll see Akira
Look down, Junzaka
And to be honest, Yuzu and the others' mentality
Surprisingly, you know, it's a quiet situation, because there are so many people
We have to shout in the midst of them.
Running along the side
So that's why we need to have the mentality too.
We need to get into our own world.
We don't care what's going on around us.
There's nobody running around us.
That's right.
That's why we need to be mental
That's why.
It's a team effort.
Oh, no.
Yuzu is really nervous.
This kind of nervousness...
I'm starting to get nervous.
I'm not supposed to sit down.
You're telling me not to be nervous.
I'm nervous.
Shall we dance with the boys?
Let's dance as boys.
I'll dance with the boys.
What do you want to do?
Let's do the seiri.
That's it.
Let's do the pickle.
Pickles.
Yes, sir.
Drink it.
serve in a cup
bless you
no connection
len
boo boo soon
It's starting. I'm a little confused because of that new area.
Yes, everyone has come to cheer us on, thank you.
Thank you very much.
It's not "go hard".
That's all for now.
The show will air on TBS Sasuke 2023 on December 27th at 6pm.
TBS Sasuke 2023!
Bye-bye!